Hello, I'm looking for a game I love called Her.
I'm looking for a game I love to play called Her.
Yes, I do.
You have to do something about the subject.
I'm not very good at explaining.
I'm like, "Who was that?
Game Master
It's a game of "I didn't know that".
Game master? Yes, that's right.
If you watch, you'll understand.
Please watch to the end, click the "Good" button, and subscribe to our channel.
I'm the type of guy who says it first.
Boo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo hoo
I don't know if it's that funny.
Let's start with Ailee.
Yes, sir.
Okay, let's do this.
I'll have Ailee do the why.
Let me show you.
Why? Why? Why?
Let's have Ailee play this card.
Yes, sir.
This means we're all supposed to keep our eyes down.
One at a time.
Okay, then.
I'll do it.
Okay.
That's it.
Okay, let's have Ailee do it.
Here we go.
Why? Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
I don't know. It's hard.
I don't know.
All right, all right, all right.
I'll say it one last time
Se-no.
Ehhhh...
Why are you so strong?
What's wrong with it?
Oh, no!
Wow.
What's the right answer?
Let's see what you got.
Curry shop order.
Why?
I don't know.
It makes you look grumpy.
Why?
When you're rejected.
Why not?
You're not the type to get angry.
Why am I?
My boy's the bad one.
I'll fix it.
I don't know why I said that.
What did I just say?
You talk too much.
Maybe that's why she dumped me.
Let's go next, Ten-san.
Here's your subject, Mr. Ten.
Oh, no.
Oh...
Okay, the alphabet is...
Thank you.
Thank you. Close your eyes.
Close your eyes.
This one.
Here you go, gal.
Bon appétit!
Polár På, João.
Ugh, it's so hard!
I tried to make it a little harder to understand.
How's that? How's that? How's that?
You want to see it again?
Boo-hoo-hoo!
Boo-boo-boo.
Boo-boo-boo!
waits like a hardened 셨 Wert even bothered
good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good good
Hey, it's YouTube!
I'm here, I'm pickupn m 국村兎山 hoped
I'm looking forward to your next 60 Christina
If you're a bit girly for the sake of the girly-girly style, my friend, laughed at us!
This is it!
Ohhhhhh!
Okay, okay, let's hide it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, let's go, then. - Okay.
Oh, no. Yeah.
But it's difficult.
Am I a person?
No, you should think of me as a cat.
If you do it as a cat...
You should feel like a cat, right?
I'm with you, I'm with you, I'm with you.
I'm with you. I'm with you.
I should be more human, right?
I think I'll go with that.
I think I know why we're doing this.
Okay. - Okay.
Okay?
Shy.
Okay.
G
H
C
Scarier than that.
We broke up.
That's great. - What?
Meow at the cat.
Meow.
I don't have time for this kind of fighting.
Can I be game master too?
You can be the game master.
It's all about facial expressions.
Facial expressions are important.
I'll leave it at that.
Yes, sir.
Yes?
Yes when he knocks
Yes when cutting back.
Yes when checking for bleeding
Yes without motivation
Yes when giving a gift
Yes when angry
Yes when confession is OK
Yes when you are ready to confess
Close your eyes.
I made a mistake.
You were looking at me.
Is that okay?
Yes, I'm ready.
Yes, sir.
Okay. - Okay.
What? That was? Yeah, yeah.
What?
No? One more time.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I've seen that face before.
I've seen that face before. I know it! I know it!
Shall we do it now? Okay.
Okay, M!
No, no, no.
What? Wait a minute. Didn't you get this from the manager?
Yeah, he's just smiling.
Is that D? Is it a D? Is it an unmotivated D?
Final Lancer? Final Lancer?
Final Lancer. No.
But Kira-san would say "E" when she gives him the present.
I wonder if Kira-san would say it like that when he gave her the present.
C? Final Lancer?
No. What? Wait a minute.
Do it again. Okay.
Oh, H?
It's an H. Uh, no, no, no, wait a minute.
When you do the 5-nation thing, it's really like that. Real? Real? Real? Real.
Oh!
Yeah! Please, will you go?
Yes! Yes!
I can't hear you around here anymore.
Huh! Haa! Huh!
Are you there? Are you there?
So, who were you when you were playing Okkala?
Yes, sir.
Uh, sure.
I don't know him very well.
He's cute.
The other day, when nothing was going on...
During rehearsal, really.
Then they said they were going to play some music, and when everyone was moving...
Ten-san, without warning...
Kira is just like A, right?
He was talking bad about her.
Like A? No, wait. Without warning.
A is cute.
She said that out of nowhere.
You want me to do it? A.
A?
Where's A?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hmm? But just a normal face.
It's a normal face.
What?
A?
Let me do another yes!
Yes, when I ask you back.
Yes?
Uh...
Yes, when you confirm your old seat.
Yes!
When you ask back?
A.
A
A when you ask back
Can you do A for Sakurazaka?
What do you mean, "A for Sakurazaka"?
Can you do an A for Sakurazaka?
Can you do A for Sakurazaka?
Sakurazaka46
Is it that funny?
I hope you get a bad card.
Please do this!
This one! Let's all play together!
They're squeezing.
Did you show it to the camera? Yes, I did.
Okay, okay.
This is hard.
I won't let you do it, es Sync.
An.
I like it.
LOL!
A is OK with me.
I'll get him to do it right.
It's just a normal like.
I think I got it.
Okay.
It's not A.
It's not an A.
A.
A is...
It was a D.
Was C
A.
That was difficult.
What do you mean, "I love you"?
I'm sorry about the A.
Look at the camera.
Let's just get one shot.
With A.
I love it.
And this one.
Come on in.
Okay, bye.
I'd like to play Jenga.
I've come up with a great idea for a penalty game.
I don't care what you say to the camera.
I like the idea of making you do something.
I've been thinking up all kinds of punishment games for the camera.
I'm always thinking
It's not good.
So this time, I'm going to make you say goodbye to the camera.
Oh, man.
What's wrong?
If you ever run out...
Maybe we could change it up every other round or something.
If it floats your boat.
Something you've done recently
something you've done
Something that goes from the bottom of that
The formation below
What I've done recently
I left it at a hotel in Miyazaki.
Did you get the charger?
That's why I chose that theme.
No, it's not.
Where's the black one?
I don't know.
What have you done recently?
What's the latest thing I've done?
Yesterday...
I couldn't open the lid of a jar of raayu
I couldn't open it at all.
I was going to use my clothes to open it.
The clothes I was wearing at the time
White fluffy pajamas
I'd recently bought.
I got a little bit of raayu on it.
And I was like, "Gah!
I don't know.
I'm so fucked up.
I got a fluffy pair of pajamas.
I got a little bit of raayu on me.
Okay, I'll stand over here.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Yay!
I woke up 15 minutes before we left today.
I woke up.
15 minutes before I wanted to leave.
I'm up.
It's amazing how people don't hesitate.
Do you know what Champéry is?
I'm really into it.
It's what you drink when you're having a party.
Do you usually drink it?
Do you drink it on a regular basis?
Yes, I do.
Perntelettes.
Pishaw!
Did they all go to spill it?
They did it twice.
Oh, my God.
Wow, they're really getting used to it.
That's nice.
I had school.
I had to teach school.
I didn't even tell her why.
I didn't tell the teacher.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You can't do that.
I thought we had a rule that if you touch something once, you have to take it away.
What?
Oh, there's someone who's a pain in the ass like that.
What a thing to say.
Take this off, and it's a little off.
It's like, "Oh, no!
Some people are such a pain in the ass.
If you want to touch me all you want...
I'll tell you about my recent shopping blunders.
Why did you fail?
Oh, uh, uh, uh, uh...
I bought two of them.
I somehow got the size wrong.
Like this.
Oh no!
That's why I'm not good at shopping online
Knit like this
Like this.
What do you mean?
English knit!
Can I borrow your shoes?
Your face.
You don't look so bad.
Can I have some milk?
I was going to drink something
I wanted to grow up.
Not two liters.
Two liters is too big.
I used a liter.
I couldn't drink it.
I don't know, it's all expired.
I'm so sorry
I'm so sorry, it was such a waste!
I'm sorry.
You don't understand.
I really did it!
Oh, wow!
That's good.
That was good.
I was pretty aggressive.
That's great.
Oh, wow.
I found it.
Can I push back?
Oh, no, it's just a simple "why not?
It's a simple what the hell?
Simple what the hell?
It's on the concrete.
You know those little red things on the concrete?
Uh...
When they get crushed...
They're really... they're all over the concrete at the local park.
Did you say you were crushing them?
You were crushing them?
Stop it.
With your hands?
It's kind of hard on me, too.
Huh.
There's a really good balance.
It was pretty bad.
It's an ant.
Have you ever been bitten by one?
No, I haven't.
It hurts.
It hurts a lot.
I used to collect ants.
I collected a lot of ants.
I made a house full of them.
He bit me on the thumb.
It hurts, doesn't it?
If only Marut, the maratan shop owner, were here...
Oh, no!
He fell down.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God!
It's so good!
I was just passing a maratan restaurant.
Oh, oh, oh!
It's down! This one's down!
Aah! Aah!
Don't go this way!
Oh!
I'm sure the real thing was a reflex, too, when you saw what was under the balance.
Well, I just wanted to talk to you... about what?
He's not so nice lately. He's nice, but he's always looking at other girls.
I don't like it... and I've been holding it back... but it's just too much.
I want to break up with him.
I can't tell you, Dad.
I played the guitar game, but to be honest, it was more like my turn to play the Bach.
Boo-boo.
Okay, A-bunch, say bye-bye, everybody.
Okay, A-Leader.
A leader for a minute.
Okay, A for old.
Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
If you think Jen would like to play with us
Good button and subscribe to our channel!
Okay.
A
A.
See you soon.
Subscribe to our channel!